<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QwizApp</string>
    <string name="term_conditions">Terms &amp; Condition</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">771411263364870</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb771411263364870</string>

    <string name="googleclientId">674238667170-u6lnim30rpp3f7cne8tmvnt8e2ejrel5.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="googleclientSecret">kAibSYnoltoh4lZyCrTMNTFS</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="Old_Password">Old Password</string>
    <string name="New_Password">New Password</string>
    <string name="Confirm_Password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="slogen">\" Earn, Learn, Publish and Go \"</string>

    <string name="help">help</string>
    <string name="quit">quit</string>
    <string name="string_help_text">Need for help !</string>
    <string name="settings">settings</string>
    <string name="string_choose_image">Choose image</string>
    <string name="privacy"><b>Something about Qwizapp And Key features</b>\nQwizapp Is premium App and Install for free for anyone.\nYou Can Learn by Attend The endless Quiz and Together you will get Money per Question Answer surely 100 % in your wallet quickly.\nYou can earn money unlimited by attend the endless questions, Also you can Publish Your Own Unique Question on our App and Can Earn Unlimited Money from Our unlimited Users Also.\nRefer Qwizapp to your friends to earn more Money per install (You will Get USD 1.00, Or INR70 RUPEES or 10000 Points per refer and install).\nYou can earn rewards and money also by watch ad videos from our app.\nYou can get instant Money or rewards while Attending Quiz, watching Ad videos, Publish Your Own Questions, So don’t wait longer, First install Our Qwizapp And use then you have to decide that how we are better from Others.\nEarn money anytime, anywhere, simply by install Our Qwizapp for free. \nWe have the most reliable rewards app with features that allow users to earn cash immediately by Different –Different way Like From (Watch Ads, Attend Quiz, Publish Own Questions, and by Refer Simply),
\n\n** (First use then believe on QWIZAPP) **\n
<b>How to Earn Money and how can withdraw the earned Cash or Rewards:-</b>\nKindly First Install the Qwizapp and register by Genuine Details and then you have to choose your interested area for earning on the app platform and then you can start the money making.\nQWIZAPP will give you 10 points for watch ad videos.\nQWIZAPP will give you 10 points for attend questions for right answers.\nQWIZAPP will give you 10 points from your every Audience user who will give answers for your question.
\nQWIZAPP will give you 10,000 points for every install where you will refer.\nYou will convert your all Points Immediately to your wallet and can use that money for purchase the plan and can do request for withdraw that money.\nIf you want to earn huge money then you have to publish your own unique question and earn unlimited.\nYou can use only 50 % earned money for purchasing.\nYou will get your earn money in your bank details after withdraw request to Qwizapp.\nNon-Refund Policy and restrictions and Privacy\nWe don’t have any refund policy.\nQwizapp will not share your any kind of information to any others. So don’t worry about your any details.\nKindly don’t use any adults words or any other type of negative words while publish your questions at the app.\nQwizapp will not show your publish questions to other users if find against restrictions.\nKindly give us suggestions for any kind of changes/Problems…others Our Qwizapp Team Will solve as soon as possible.
\n
\n<b>Thanks &amp; Regards.</b>\nQwizapp Team</string>
    <string name="underline_name"><u>QwizApp</u></string>
</resources>
